Finding aid for the June L. Mazer Lesbian Archive Collection of Audio Materials, 1970-1999 LSC.2230
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Groups Alphabetized by Group/Topic Cassettes, 1975-1995; Series 19.; 59 audio cassette tapes
  - Various Artists: An Historical Sampling of Women Composers & the Music (Middle Ages to the Present), 1986; audio cassette tape (Box 1, Folder 6, Item 19)
    Side 1: Music for the Mass by Nun Composers, The Romantic Handel, Nineteenth Century Lieder, For the Flute, Bela Bartok Quintet for Piano and Strings, Trios for violin, cello, and piano. Side 2: String quartets, Music for Flute and Strings by Three Americans, New Music from New England, Poems and Magic, Karel Husa, Priaulx Rainier, On the Edge.
    Copyright 1986 Leonarda Productions, Inc.
- Reading Performances 1980-83, 1980-1983; Series 2.; 38 audio cassette tapes
  Contains Reading performances by a variety of lesbian and feminist writers including Judy Grahn, Peg Crukshank, Judy Freespirit, Kent Hyde, Elsa Gidlow, Pat Bond, Beverly Smith, Terri de la Pena and others. These readings range in audio quality and were recorded at lesbian bars, bookstores, events and on KFPA radio.
  - 1 Radio Performance Tape 1 of 2: KPFA "Twelve Years of Lesbianism", 27 June 1981; audio cassette tape (Box 2, Folder 1, Item 1)
    Sections of a radio documentary on the history of lesbian activism featuring a lot of music. Included is a discussion on ways to donate to the SCWU and feminist music.
    Tape 2 will not play. Included is the first and third sections of the documentary.
  - 2 Radio Performance: KPFA "The West Coast Lesbian Collections, 21 November 81; audio cassette tape (Box 2, Folder 1, Item 2)
    A history and explanation of the West Coast Lesbian Collection Archive.
    Includes many interviews and readings.
  - 4 Reading Performance Arobateau, Red (Selections), 23 September 1981; audio cassette tape (Box 2, Folder 1, Item 3-4)
    Reading Performance of stories concerning transsexuality and prostitution.
    Audio Quality is poor
  - 3 Reading Performances: Judy Grahn "We Go Round The World" and "Butch/Femme", 12 June 1981; audio cassette tape (Box 2, Folder 1, Item 5)
    Begins with a discussion of Persephone Press. Side One includes selections from "We Go Round the World," a story detailing the history of non-western gay cultures and terminologies.
    Side Two could not be recorded
  - 7 Reading Performance "Bridge Called My Back", 12 November 1981; audio cassette tape (Box 2, Folder 1, Item 6-7)
    Includes group reading performances of Bridge Called My Back and other stories.
    Poor Audio Quality
  - 2 Reading Performances: Tape 2 of 2 Grahn, Judy "Queen of Bulldykery" and "Butches/Fems", 29 May 1981; audio cassette tape (Box 2, Folder 1, Item 8)
    Includes a performance concerning Nazis and lesbians along with a musical performance
  - 9 Reading Performance Cruikshank, Peg, 2 December 1981; audio cassette tape (Box 2, Folder 1, Item 9)
    Cruikshank reading works to commemorate the opening of the archives. Includes stories by Linda Marie, Marilyn Hacker, Peg Cruickshank, Cordova, Susan Cavin, Doris Davenport, Nancy Manahan and others. Many of the stories concern women discovering and exploring their lesbian sexuality. The tape ends with a discussion on liberalism and gay politics.
    Tape ends in the middle of a story.
  - 16 Reading Performance "Daddys Girl" Judy Freespirit, 26 January 1981; audio cassette tape (Box 2, Folder 1, Item 10)
    Contains a story concerning incest, sexuality and abuse.
    Possibly from 1982 instead of 1981
  - 10 Reading Performance Mitchell, R. and Canaan, A., 13 December 1981; audio cassette tape (Box 2, Folder 1, Item 11)
    Noise musical performance followed by readings.
    Badly Recorded
  - Judy Grahn at Ollie's Bar "Sashay Down the Lavender Trail" and "skeletons in Sgt. Kirk's Closet", 15 May 1981; audio cassette tape (Box 2, Folder 1, Item 12)
    Side 1 contains "Sashay Down the Lavender Trail."
    Side 2 contains "Skeletons in Sgt. Kirk's Closet."
  - Judy Grahn at Ollie's Bar, Oakland, Ca., 29 May 1981; audio cassette tape (Box 2, Folder 1, Item 13)
    Side 1 contains "Butches and Femmes" and Side 2 contains "Queen of BullDykery"
  - 5 Reading Performance Tape 1 of 2 Grahn, Judy "Queen of Bulldykery", 12 January 1980; audio cassette tape (Box 2, Folder 1, Item 14)
    Unplayable
  - no.17 Reading Performance tape 2 of 2 Narratives by C. Clarke 5.83, May 1983; audio cassette tape (Box 2, Folder 2, Item 1)
    performance by C. Clarke
    unplayable
  - no14 Reading Performance Tape 2 of 2 Beverly Smith, 1 July 1982; audio cassette tape (Box 2, Folder 2, Item 2)
    Dramatic reading at Old Wive's Tales, San Francisco, Ca.
  - no14 Reading Performance Tape 1 of 2 Beverly Smith, 1 July 1982; audio cassette tape (Box 2, Folder 2, Item 3)
  - no17 Reading Performance Tape 1 of 2 by C. Clarke, May 1983; audio cassette tape (Box 2, Folder 2, Item 4)
    Dramatic reading with a lot of audience noise.
    side two is blank
  - no13 Reading Performance tape 1 of 2 Elsa Gidlow, 29 July 1982; audio cassette tape (Box 2, Folder 2, Item 5-6)
    Dramatic Reading at Old Wive's Tales in San Francisco, Ca. Side one includes poetry and side two includes an autobiography of early years in New York.
  - no11 Reading Performance Freespirit, Robbins, etc., undated (Box 2, Folder 2, Item 7)
    Reading with lots of audience noise.
  - no11 Reading Performance Tape 1 Freespirit, Robbins, Elizabeth, undated; audio cassette tape (Box 2, Folder 2, Item 8)
    reading with lots of noise.
  - no15 Reading Performance Publishing by Barbara Grier Faultline by SHeila O. Taylor, undated; audio cassette tape (Box 2, Folder 2, Item 9-10)
    oral history on lesbian publishing and Barbar Grier's experience in the field
  - no7 Musical Performance Tape 1 of 1 Naked Keys by m. Adams, 1980; audio cassette tape (Box 2, Folder 2, Item 11)
    piano music
  - no5 Theatre Performance tape 1 of 1 By Popular Demand, undated; audio cassette tape (Box 2, Folder 2, Item 12)
    largely audience noise
    badly recorded
  - no 4 Theatre Performance Bond, Pat, Murder in the WACS Valencia Rose, S.F., 28 June 1983; audio cassette tape (Box 2, Folder 2, Item 13)
    Comedy routine about homosexual culture
  - Terri de la Pena Reading at the Mazer Collection, 24 September 1989; audio cassette tape (Box 2, Folder 2, Item 14)
    autobiography of latina lesbian exploring her sexuality and figuring out how to become a writer
  - no6 Reading Performance Tape 1 Hyde, Kent Selections, undated; audio cassette tape (Box 2, Folder 2, Item 15)
    poetry reading including The Wedge, The Generations, Prelude, Poetry,
    Celebration for Rudy, General William Booth Enters Heaven
  - no3 Radio Performance tape 1 of 1 Fear of Fat, undated; 6/19/1980 (Box 2, Folder 2, Item 16)
    Judy Freespirit on KPFA discussing fat and her story Fear of Fat
  - no3 Theatre Performance Bond, Pat Muder in the Wacs, 27 February 1982; audio cassette tape (Box 2, Folder 2, Item 17)
    comedy routine concerning lesbian culture
  - no1 Theatre Performance tape 1 Tomlin, Lily Modern Scream, 1975; audio cassette tape (Box 2, Folder 2, Item 18)
    comedy routine commercial tape
- Jewish Issues Cassettes, 1980-1990; Series 3.; 20 audio cassette tapes
  Recordings of Jewish Feminist and lesbian conferences and discussions
  - Berkeley Jewish Lesbians Conference, March 1982; audio cassette tape (Box 2, Folder 3, Item 1-2)
    closing remarks from conference, including complaints concerning the conference from special interest groups
  - 7th annual NWSA Convention Feminist Jewish Womyn's Voices Creating Choices through Feminist Education, 22 June 1985; audio cassette tape (Box 2, Folder 3, Item 3)
    side one includes Jo Cochran
    side 2 includes Barbara Smith on racism in women's studies and Barbara Macdonald discussing ageism in academia
  - Judy Grahn at BCC Temple, undated; audio cassette tape (Box 2, Folder 3, Item 4)
    Short stories and speech on lesbian etymologies
  - Jewish Conference?, undated; audio cassette tape (Box 2, Folder 3, Item 5)
  - New Jewish Agenda, undated; audio cassette tape (Box 2, Folder 3, Item 6)
  - Jewish Lesbian Culture and Anti-Semitism in the Lesbian Community, 27 February 1983; audio cassette tape (Box 2, Folder 3, Item 7-8)
    Presentation by Minneapolis, Minnesota Jewish Lesbians recorded at A Woman's Coffeehouse
  - Dovida Goodwoman, Jewish Women's Event, undated; audio cassette tape (Box 2, Folder 3, Item 9)
    instrumental music and songs
  - NWSA Jewish Woman's Plenary, 1986; audio cassette tape (Box 2, Folder 3, Item 10)
    plenary on feminism, judaism and lesbians. Includes talk on jews in the media
  - Jewish Feminist Conference Party, 6 February 1982; audio cassette tape (Box 2, Folder 3, Item 11)
    sounds of a party and bellydancing
  - The Lost Generation Produced y Lani Silver and Ruth Linden, 1983; audio cassette tape (Box 2, Folder 3, Item 12)
    side one is Jerusalem: Survivors Gather
    side two is The Lost Generation. Mostly Oral histories of Holocaust survivors created by the Holocaust Media Project
  - New Jewish Agenda Conference IMRU-KPFK, 5 July 1987; audio cassette tape (Box 2, Folder 3, Item 13)
    Radio program on how to be a gay activist. Ends with news stories and an interview with someone from NAMBLA
  - Non-Jewish Wimmin of Color on Anti-Semitism, 30 May 1982; audio cassette tape (Box 2, Folder 3, Item 14)
    presentations by women of color on anti-semitism
  - no12 Reading Performance Jewish lesbian Writers Group, 15 April 1982; audio cassette tape (Box 2, Folder 3, Item 15-16)
    Stories on intersections between jewisha nd feminist issues
  - Anti-Semitism for Non-Jews, 30 May 1982; audio cassette tape (Box 2, Folder 3, Item 17-19)
    Lois Helmbold facilitates presentations on anti-semitism
  - Working Meeting on Feminist media and jewish feminist issues, 30 May 1982; audio cassette tape (Box 2, Folder 3, Item 20)
    Presntation on feminist and jewish issues
- Shadows of Aggar by Chris Anne Wolf, 1991; Series 13.; 12 audio cassette tapes
  Recording, on 12 audio cassette tapes, of the science-fiction novel, Shadows of Aggar, by Chris Anne Wolf and published in 1991. 308 pages. Shadows of Aggar is Book One of the Amazons of Aggar Trilogy. Story centers around Diana n'Athena, who is an Amazon working for the Terran empire on the planet of Aggar. Diana is on a mission to rescue a downed pilot, but she is forced to be bonded with a Shadow, Elena, in order to fulfill her mission. The two women develop a relationship as they strive to prevent intergalactic war. Author Chris Anne Wolf died in 1997.
  - Shadows of Aggar, 1991; audio cassette tape (Box 2, Folder 4, Item 1-12)
    Pages 1-21. Shadows of Aggar is by Chris Anne Wolf and was published in 1991. Shadows of Aggar is Book One of the Amazons of Aggar Trilogy. Story centers around Diana n'Athena, who is an Amazon working for the Terran empire on the planet of Aggar. Diana is on a mission to rescue a downed pilot, but she is forced to be bonded with a Shadow, Elena, in order to fulfill her mission. The two women develop a relationship as they strive to prevent intergalactic war. Author Chris Anne Wolf died in 1997.
- Interviews Cassettes, 1973-1991; Series 8.; 34 audio cassette tapes
  - "Us" - Nora, undated; audio cassette tape (Box 2, Folder 5, Item 1)
  - Susan Stoffer at MCC Conference 1981, 23 May 1981; audio cassette tape (Box 2, Folder 5, Item 2)
  - SCWU - "Patty and Laura", 1983; audio cassette tape (Box 2, Folder 5, Item 3)
    Recording of a complete 3-act play titled "Patty and Laura."
  - Interview with Penny Johnson, 20 October 1982; audio cassette tape (Box 2, Folder 5, Item 4)
  - Barbara Grier Sojourner Interview, 29 July 1979; audio cassette tape (Box 2, Folder 5, Item 5)
  - Mary Nunn, 30 July 1979; audio cassette tape (Box 2, Folder 5, Item 6)
  - Dorothy Matson, undated; audio cassette tape (Box 2, Folder 5, Item 7)
  - KPFK L.G. Day, 7 July 1991; audio cassette tape (Box 2, Folder 5, Item 8)
    Includes: 1. Part 2 of SCWU Interview on heterosexism 2. GLAAD interview with Josey Catogio 3. Police interview re: crimes and treatment 4. Interview with two nice girls by Lori Megdovich
  - Estelle Freedman - "Our Sister's Keeper", 21 May 1981; audio cassette tape (Box 2, Folder 5, Item 9)
    Book promotional interview with Estelle Freedman for "Our Sister's Keeper."
  - Fat Lip Theater, 19 August 1982; audio cassette tape (Box 2, Folder 5, Item 10)
    Information written in cassette case: Fat Lip Outakes Old Wives Tales San Francisco Fat Lip Theater Judy Freespirit
  - Fat - A meeting Elana Dykewoman, reading, undated; audio cassette tape (Box 2, Folder 5, Item 11)
    Announcements, readings at a Fat Sisters meeting. Includes a reading by Elana Dykewoman.
  - Breathing Room Interview Kris Welch Morning Show, 5 December 1982, 4 January 1983; audio cassette tape (Box 2, Folder 5, Item 12)
    Side 1: 12/5/1982, 6AM, Breathing Room interview with Randy Alfred on KSAN, "The Gay Life."
    Side 2: 1/4/1983, 8AM, Kris Welch Morning Show on KPFA
  - Linda Albertano, Goldminers of '86., 29 April 1986; audio cassette tape (Box 2, Folder 5, Item 13)
    Linda J. Albertano, Goldminers of '86, on KPFK
  - Linda Albertano, "Gold Miners of '86" Waynna Kato, "I.D. Art", 29 April 1986; audio cassette tape (Box 2, Folder 5, Item 14)
  - Oral History Interview, Rikki, July 1981; audio cassette tape (Box 2, Folder 5, Item 15-16)
    Tape 1 of 2
  - Interview with Ann Bannon, June 1983; audio cassette tape (Box 2, Folder 5, Item 17)
    Charlotte Rubens interviews Ann Bannon
    Tape 2 of 2
  - Our Lesbian Roots "Crack in the Closet Door" Valerie Taylor, 1980; audio cassette tape (Box 2, Folder 5, Item 18)
    Part 2 in Valerie Taylor's lecture series about lesbian history.
  - Interviews: Kitty Tsui(Stanford Poetry Conference), 17 April 1982; audio cassette tape (Box 2, Folder 6, Item 1)
    Sally Thomas and Margaret Jensen interview Kitty Tsui at the Stanford Women's Poetry Conference.
  - Phyllis - Interview on Movement Carolyn, undated; audio cassette tape (Box 2, Folder 6, Item 2)
    Side 1: Phyllis - Interview on movement
    Side 2: Carolyn
  - Barbara Grier Sojourner Interview, 29 July 1979; audio cassette tape (Box 2, Folder 6, Item 3)
  - Susan Zemel Interview for Advocate, undated; audio cassette tape (Box 2, Folder 6, Item 4)
    Interview with Sue Zemel for Advocate
  - Remembering Stonewall, undated; audio cassette tape (Box 2, Folder 6, Item 5)
    Remembering Stonewall radio program from KPFK. Side 2 is interview with Robin Morgan.
  - Dale Spender, "Women know the Whole Story, Men Know Only Half", undated; audio cassette tape (Box 2, Folder 6, Item 6)
    Radio program from KPFK.
  - 90.7 FM KPFK 7PM Wed + Mondays, undated; audio cassette tape (Box 2, Folder 6, Item 7)
    Radio programs from KPFK:
    Wednesday - Feminist Magazine Hour
    Monday - IMRU
  - Slides, circa 1984; audio cassette tape (Box 2, Folder 6, Item 8)
    Transcribed from paper in cassette case:
    Slides -
    From Ret's Air Force scrapbook 1951
    Tape - Bunny asked Ret to say something about each slide as it was projected on the wall; this was around 1984.
    For more info see Ret in the film BEFORE STONEWALL; also see transcript of her B4 Stonewall interview in its entirety.
  - Feminist Magazine Hour (Wed 7-8pm), undated; audio cassette tape (Box 2, Folder 6, Item 9)
  - Dykes Resist!, 1983; audio cassette tape (Box 2, Folder 6, Item 10)
    First Hand Accounts of Lesbians Fighting Male Violence. Produced by Radical Rose Recordings.
  - Joan Robbins Interviewed by Nancy Matthews, 20 February 1988; audio cassette tape (Box 2, Folder 6, Item 11-12)
  - I'm in Love with Lesbians, 1983; audio cassette tape (Box 2, Folder 6, Item 13)
    An Interview with Maxine Feldman, Lesbian-Feminist Musician and Comic. Produced by Radical Rose Recordings.
  - Herstory Taping SCWU, 25 February 1989; audio cassette tape (Box 2, Folder 6, Item 14-15)
  - #14 Auto/Bio Tape 2 of 3 J. Phelps and B. MacCulloch, April 1982; audio cassette tape (Box 2, Folder 6, Item 16)
- Women Writers Read Their Work, 1976-1986; Series 15.; 37 audio cassette tapes
  Recordings of women writers reading and discussing their work poetry readings, poetry performances, radio shows, and professionally-recorded poetry. Authors included are Eloise Klein Healy, Adrienne Rich, Anne Sexton, Alice Bloch, Aleida Rodriguez, Ann Nietzke, Mitsuye Yamada, Nellie Wong, Honor Moore, Wanda Coleman, and others.
  - Eloise Klein Healy: A Packet Beating Like a Heart, [ca. 1980s]; audio cassette tape (Box 3, Folder 2, Item 1)
    Reading performance by Eloise Klein Healy of poems from her book, A Packet Beating Like a Heart, at the Women's Building, in Los Angeles, CA, as part of the Women's Writers Program. Healy is an American poet who has published 5 books of poetry and founded Arktoi Books. Healy was also involved in the Woman's Building, the Westcoast feminist cultural center, throughout the 1970s and 1980s in various positions including teacher and Board of Directors. Healy was the Founding Chair of the MFA in Creative Writing Program at Antioch University Los Angeles, was the director of the Women's Studies Program at California State University Northridge, and was co-founder of ECO-ARTS, an eco-tourism/arts venture.
  - Eloise Klein Healy: Publication Parts for Building Change, 2 April 1976; audio cassette tape (Box 3, Folder 2, Item 2)
    Eloise Klein Healy reading to an audience from her book of poetry, Building Some Changes. Healy is an American poet who has published 5 books of poetry and founded Arktoi Books. Healy was also involved in the Woman's Building, the Westcoast feminist cultural center, throughout the 1970s and 1980s in various positions including teacher and Board of Directors. Healy was the Founding Chair of the MFA in Creative Writing Program at Antioch University Los Angeles, was the director of the Women's Studies Program at California State University Northridge, and was co-founder of ECO-ARTS, an eco-tourism/arts venture.
  - Women Writers Series: Allen, Graham, Healy, 29 May 1982; audio cassette tape (Box 3, Folder 2, Item 3)
    Recording of Women Writers Series reading performances at the Women's Building in Los Angeles, CA. Selected authors are Eloise Klein Healy, Judy Graham, and Paula Allen Gunn.
  - Eloise Klein Healy: Interviewed by Claudia Bonard, 5 December 1980; audio cassette tape (Box 3, Folder 2, Item 4)
    Recording of interview of Eloise Klein Healy by Claudia Bonard. They discuss Healy's poetry and writing, small press publishers, and her book, A Packet Beating Like a Heart-published in 1981. A Packet Beating Like a Heart is a collection poems from Los Angeles-life as seen from a car window and emotions experienced at freeways speeds. The book was first published by Books of a Feather Press. Healy and Bonard discuss the benefits of publishing with a small press, including the ability to keep control over how the book will be published.
  - Eloise Klein Healy: Interviewed by Jessica Schuman, 29 December 1978; audio cassette tape (Box 3, Folder 2, Item 5)
    Recording of interview of Eloise Klein Healy by Jessica Schuman. They discuss influences, inspiration and topics in Healy's writing, including the city of Los Angeles. Healy also reads her work. Healy is an American poet who has published 5 books of poetry and founded Arktoi Books. Healy was also involved in the Woman's Building, the Westcoast feminist cultural center, throughout the 1970s and 1980s in various positions including teacher and Board of Directors. Healy was the Founding Chair of the MFA in Creative Writing Program at Antioch University Los Angeles, was the director of the Women's Studies Program at California State University Northridge, and was co-founder of ECO-ARTS, an eco-tourism/arts venture.
  - Eloise Klein Healy: Interview on Poetry Connection, 19 March 1983; audio cassette tape (Box 3, Folder 2, Item 6)
    Eloise Klein Healy is interviewed on KPFK 90.7, Los Angeles, Pacifica Radio's Poetry Connection show. Hosts are Austin Strauss and Wanda Coleman. They discuss her career as a teacher at a high school and at universities throughout Los Angeles, her books and work, and what influences and inspires-including her youth and the city of Los Angeles-her writing. Klein also reads selected poems. Healy is an American poet who has published 5 books of poetry and founded Arktoi Books. Healy was also involved in the Woman's Building, the Westcoast feminist cultural center, throughout the 1970s and 1980s in various positions including teacher and Board of Directors. Healy was the Founding Chair of the MFA in Creative Writing Program at Antioch University Los Angeles, was the director of the Women's Studies Program at California State University Northridge, and was co-founder of ECO-ARTS, an eco-tourism/arts venture.
  - Eloise Klein Healy: Sisterhood Bookstore Minimarathon, 1 November 1982; audio cassette tape (Box 3, Folder 2, Item 7)
    In celebration of Sisterhood Bookstore's tenth anniversary, Eloise Klein Healy organized a Los Angeles women writers reading. Healy is introduced as MC of the event and goes on to discuss the agenda. Healy reads her own poetry, followed by Carol Lem reading her own. Healy is an American poet who has published 5 books of poetry and founded Arktoi Books. Healy was also involved in the Woman's Building, the Westcoast feminist cultural center, throughout the 1970s and 1980s in various positions including teacher and Board of Directors. Healy was the Founding Chair of the MFA in Creative Writing Program at Antioch University Los Angeles, was the director of the Women's Studies Program at California State University Northridge, and was co-founder of ECO-ARTS, an eco-tourism/arts venture.
  - Judy Grahn: Women Writers Series, 29 May 1982; audio cassette tape (Box 3, Folder 2, Item 8)
    Judy Grahn reads Plain Song and other poems for the Women Writers Series, organized by the Women's Building in Los Angeles, CA. Grahn is an American poet and writer. Her work focuses on feminist and lesbian issues. Grahn has written and published in 12 books. Grahn was a member of the Gay Women's Liberation Group, the first lesbian-feminist collective on the West Coast, founded in 1969.
  - Jacqueline de Angelis: Sisterhood Bookstore Minimarathon, 1 November 1982; audio cassette tape (Box 3, Folder 2, Item 9)
    No audio on tape.
  - Jacqueline De Angelis: Interviewed by Eloise Klein Healy, 22 December 1982; audio cassette tape (Box 3, Folder 2, Item 10)
    Jacqueline De Angelis is interviewed on KPFK 90.7, Los Angeles, Pacifica Radio's Women's Words, which is hosted by Los Angeles writer, Eloise Klein Healy. De Angelis' short story book, The Main Gate, is about to be published by Paradise Press. De Angelis is also an editor at Books of a Feather Press. The two writers discuss the transition from poet to fiction writer, topics in writing, benefits of short stories, and influences and inspirations for work. De Angelis also reads some of her work.
    Audio is scratchy.
  - Doris Davenport & Frances Espana: Sisterhood Bookstore Minimarathon, 1 November 1982; audio cassette tape (Box 3, Folder 2, Item 11)
    In celebration of its' tenth anniversary, the Sisterhood Bookstore organized a Los Angeles women writers reading performance. This is a recording of Doris Davenport and Frances Espana as they read their work. Davenport is a lesbian feminist writer that has two books of poetry of her own and has been published in various anthologies and reviews.
  - Wanda Coleman & Michelle Cliff, 1 April 1983; audio cassette tape (Box 3, Folder 2, Item 12)